&gt;&gt; Hello everyone.
&gt;&gt; 大家好
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
I hope you're have a great time
我相信你们在
at WWDC so far.
WWDC 已经度过了一段愉快的时光
Allow me to introduce myself.
请允许我做一下自我介绍
My name is Brett Keating and I'm
我叫 Brett Keating
here with my colleague Frank
我将和我的同事 Frank Doepke 一起
Doepke and we're here to tell
向你们介绍
you about Apple's new Vision
Apple 的 Vision 框架
framework, so let's get started.
让我们开始吧
We're going to begin by showing
首先我们将会展示
you what Vision can do for your
Vision 可以为你们的 App
apps.
做些什么
We're going to go through a few
我们会展示一些
visual examples of the
视觉示例
algorithms that are going to be
其中用到的算法将会在
made available in the Vision
今年的 Vision 框架中
framework this year.
提供
At which point I'll hand it off
接下来会由
to Frank to talk about the
Frank 介绍
concepts behind the Vision
Vision 框架背后的概念
framework, why we designed
我们为什么要这样设计
things the way we did, what the
以及我们 API 背后的
mental model behind our API is.
思维模型是什么样的
And then we'll go a little
然后我们会进行深入的探讨
deeper and go through a code
研究一个
example.
代码示例
This code example brings
该代码示例结合了
together a few different
我们的 SDK 中
technologies in our SDK,
很多不同的技术
including Core Image, as well as
包括 Core Image 和
the brand-new Core ML framework
全新的 Core ML 框架
that we're offering this year
我们将在今年提供该框架
which enables you to put in your
你可以在框架中放入你的自定义模型
own custom models and have them
并使用
be accelerated using our
我们的硬件
hardware.
进行加速
So, let's begin with what you
现在让我们从你可以使用
can do with Vision.
Vision 做什么开始谈起
Let's start off with face
首先是
detection.
人脸识别
Now face detection is something
虽然现在我们的 SDK 中
we already have in our SDK, but
已经提供人脸识别的功能
we're offering in the Vision
但在今年的 Vision 框架中
framework new this year a face
我们将提供
detection that's based on deep
基于深度学习的
learning.
人脸识别
And you may already know that
你可能已经知道
deep learning has made
深度学习
groundbreaking changes in the
给 Vision 技术的准确性
accuracy in what we can do with
带来了突破性的改变
Vision technologies and face
人脸识别技术
detection is no exception.
也不例外
We're going to have higher
更高的准确性
precision which means fewer
意味着更少的误报
false positives, but we are also
同时我们
going to have dramatically
的重调用也会显著地增加
higher recall which means we'll
也就是说
miss less faces.
识别能力会更强
So, let's look at some of the
让我们看一下
examples of faces that we will
一些面部的例子
now be able to detect with the
现在使用 Vision 框架
Vision framework.
能够进行识别它们
For one thing, we'll be able to
首先我们能够识别
detect smaller faces.
更小的面部
We'll also be doing a better job
我们能够更好的识别
of detecting strong profiles.
明显的侧脸
We'll also do a better job
也能够更好的识别
detecting more partially
被局部遮挡的脸
occluded faces and that includes
遮挡物包括
things like hats and glasses.
帽子和眼镜
Sticking with the faces theme
关于面部的话题
for a little longer, we now are
还有一点要谈
offering in the Vision framework
在今年新的 Vision 框架中
new this year face landmarks,
我们将提供提供人脸特征点识别
what are face landmarks?
什么是人脸特征点呢
This is a constellation of
它是一系列
points that we detect on the
我们在面部检测到的点的集合
facer, things like the corners
其中包括眼角
of the eyes, the outline of the
嘴的外廓
mouth, the contour of the chin.
和下颏的轮廓
Here's an example, here's
比如说这样
another example, and one more
这样
example.
和这样
We're really excited about this
我们对此感到非常兴奋
I think there's going to be some
我相信会有很多
great apps created with this
使用这项技术的
technology.
优秀 App 出现
Next, also new this year in the
接下来是今年 Vision Framework 中
Vision framework is image
的另一项新技术
registration.
图像配准
If you don't know what image
如果你不知道图像配准是什么
registration is it's basically
简单来说
aligning two images based on the
它会根据两张图像中的特征
features that are present in
对两张图像
those images.
进行校准
You can use this for stitching
你可以使用该技术
together used for panorama kind
拼接全景
of like this example or image
如该例子所示
stacking applications.
或进行图像叠加应用
We have two different kinds, one
我们有两种不同的技术
that's translation only and one
一种是仅进行转换
that gives you for full
另一种是为你提供更加精确的
homography for greater accuracy.
完整单应性矩阵
We're also offering a few
我们也会提供一些
technologies that are already in
我们 SDK 中已有的技术
our SDK through CIDetector
现在它们可以通过 CIDetector 界面
interface.
获得
We're making them available in
我们也将在
the Vision API as well.
Vision API 中提供它们
That includes rectangle
这些技术包括矩形检测
detection as you can see, we
正如你所见
detect the sign in the picture.
我们检测出了图片中的标志
We're also doing barcode
在 Vision API 中还有
detection and recognition in the
条形码的
Vision API and text detection as
的检测与识别
well.
和文本检测
Another new technology,
另一个新技术
brand-new in the Vision
在今年的 Vision 框架中
framework this year is object
全新呈现的是
tracking.
目标追踪
You can use this to track a face
你可以使用该技术追踪面部
if you've detected a face.
在检测到面部的情况下
You can use that face rectangle
你可以将面部的矩形
as an initial condition to the
作为追踪的初始条件
tracking and then the Vision
Vision 框架将
framework will track that square
在你影片的
throughout the rest of your
余下部分
video.
追踪该矩形
Will also track rectangles and
我们可以追踪矩形
you can also define the initial
你也可以自己决定
condition yourself.
初始条件
So that's what I mean by general
这是通用模板的含义
templates, if you decide to for
比如说如果你
example, put a square around
和我一样
this wakeboarder as I have, you
用正方形框出这个冲浪选手
can then go ahead and track
接着播放影片
that.
进行追踪
You can see that we handle
可以看到
pretty large changes in scale,
大幅度的缩放
pretty large deformations fairly
和扭曲变形并没有影响追踪
robustly with this technology.
表明该技术较为稳定
Another really exciting
另一项激动人心的
technology that's new in Apple's
今年 Apple SDK 的新技术
SDK this year Core ML and you
是 Core ML
can integrate your Core ML
并且你可以将你的 Core ML 模型
models directly into Vision.
直接集成到 Vision 中
As I've mentioned, machine
正如我所说
learning does great things for
机器学习对
Computer Vision and you can use
计算机视觉做出了很大的贡献
Core ML if you want to create
你可以使用 Core ML
your own models, do your own
如果你想要创建自己的模型
solution.
做出自己的解决方案
Perhaps for example, you want to
比如说你可能想要
create a wedding application
创建一个婚礼应用
where you're able to detect this
用于识别婚礼中
part of the wedding is the
何时应该举行婚宴
reception, this part of the
何时
wedding is where the bride is
新娘应该
walking down the aisle.
步入走廊
If you want to train your own
如果你想要训练
model and you have the data to
自己的模型
train your own model you can do
并且你有足够的数据进行训练
that.
那你能够这样做
Core ML as I mentioned, provides
正如我提到的 Core ML
native acceleration for custom
为自定义模型提供本地加速
models so they'll run really
使它们能够快速运行
fast and Vision provides the
Vision 提供了支持这些模型的
imaging pipeline to support
成像流水线
these models, so you won't have
因此你不需要
to do any rescaling or anything
进行任何的重新调节或类似操作
like that we'll take care of all
我们将
that for you.
负责一切
We know what your model is
我们知道你的模型需要什么
expecting and we'll put the
我们会提供
image in the right format.
正确格式的图像
If you're interested in Core ML
如果你对 Core ML 感兴趣
there's some sessions that you
你可以参加其他一些的会议
can go to, we've listed the labs
下方列出了
down here for you.
研究室的名称
One of them will be tomorrow
有一场是在明天早上
morning and then another one on
另一场是在
Friday afternoon.
周五下午
So that's basically the features
基本上
that are in the Vision
这些就是 Vision 框架中的
framework.
特点
Overall, what Apple's new Vision
总的来说 Apple 全新的
framework provides are
Vision 框架为计算机视觉问题
high-level on-device solutions
提供了高层的设备内解决方案
to Computer Vision problems
并且仅靠
through one simple API.
一个简单的 API 实现
Now let me break this statement
现在让我们稍微具体一点
down just a little bit.
分析这段叙述
What do I mean by high-level
什么是高层的
solutions?
解决方案
Well we don't want you to have
我们不需要你
to be a Computer Vision expert
是计算机视觉专家
to put the magic of Computer
才能在你的应用中使用
Vision into your applications.
计算机视觉的神奇功能
You don't want to necessarily
你也不想必须了解
have to know which feature
要使用的是哪一个
detector you want to use in
特征探测器
combination with what classifier
要与什么分类器
or set of classifiers, we're
或分类器组结合
going to handle that for you or
我们会为你解决这些问题
whether or not you want to use
说实话
machine learning for example.
你是否想要使用机器学习
If you're a developer you're
如果你是开发人员
probably thinking I just want to
你可能会想
know where the faces are.
我只想要知道面部的位置
And so, we're going to handle
因此我们会为你解决
all that complexity for you.
所有复杂的过程
Depending on your use case we'll
根据你的使用场景
be doing either traditional
我们会选择使用传统方案
approach if that's what's needed
如果你的应用确实需要如此
for maybe real-time applications
比如说一些实时应用
or deep learning algorithms for
或者使用深度学习算法
higher accuracy.
以获得更高的精确性
Now I also mentioned that we're
我也说到
doing all these algorithms on
所有的算法都会在设备内实现
the device, let's talk a little
让我们介绍一下
bit about why we'd want to do
为什么我们希望
things on device versus provided
在设备内进行处理
a cloud-based solution.
而不是提供基于云的解决方案
First of all, it's privacy.
首先这是隐私问题
As you know, Apple cares a lot
你们知道
about privacy, I care a lot
Apple 非常重视隐私
about privacy working at Apple,
我在 Apple 工作时也非常重视隐私
sometimes it makes my job a
有时这会增加
little harder, but nonetheless
工作难度
keeping all your data on the
但将你所有的数据保存在设备中
device is the best way to
是保护你用户
protect your user's data
数据隐私的
privacy.
最好方法
Furthermore, with certain
此外
cloud-based solutions there's a
基于云的解决方法
cost associated with it.
会带来相关成本
If you're a developer maybe
如果你是开发人员
you're paying usage fees to use
你可能要为基于云的解决方案
a cloud-based solution.
支付使用费
Your users will have to transfer
你的用户则必须
the data to that cloud.
将数据转移到云中
All these costs they can add up
因此会增加
for both the developers and the
开发人员和用户的
users.
成本
So, when everything's on the
而当所有数据都在设备上时
device it's free.
就是免费的
And you can support real-time
你可以支持实时
use cases like the tracking
使用场景就像
example I showed you.
之前我展示的对象追踪例子一样
Imagine trying to track
想象一下
something through a video by
要在影片中追踪某个对象
sending every frame to the
需要将每一帧上传到云
cloud, I don't think that's
我不认为
going to work too well.
那是个好办法
So, no latency, fast execution
所以我们通过 Vision 框架
that's what we're offering with
提供的是一个
the Vision framework.
无延迟快速执行的解决方案
So, I hope you enjoyed that
我希望你们喜欢我的介绍
introduction, now we're going to
现在我们将要
go a little deeper and talk
深入一些
about the Vision concepts.
探讨 Vision 的概念
For this part of the
我将把
presentation I'm going to hand
这一部分的展示
it off to Frank.
交给 Frank
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thank you Brett.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢你 Brett
Hi, good afternoon, my name is
大家下午好
Frank Doepke and I'm going to
我叫 Frank Doepke
talk about more of the technical
我将更多的介绍
details what is part of our
技术细节
Vision framework.
作为 Vision 框架的一部分
So, what do we want to do, when
所以我们想做的是
we want to analyze an image we
当我们想要分析一个图像时
have three major tasks that we
实际上我们想要完成的
actually want to perform.
主要任务有三个
So, we [inaudible] finding out
第一个是询问
what is in the image and what do
找出图像里有什么
I want to know about it.
和我需要知道的是什么
There's the machinery,
第二个是处理设备
somebody's got to do the work
即完成工作的设备
and we get some results out of
第三个是结果
it, at least we hope that's
至少这是我们
what's going to happen.
希望的流程
So, in terminology for Vision
用 Vision 的术语来说
that means the asks these are
这里的询问就是
requests.
请求
And I just did a few examples
我列出了刚才的例子
here like the barcode detection
像条形码检测
or face detection and we feed
或面部识别
them into our request handler.
我们都是将请求输入 Request Handler（请求处理器）
That's the one in this case to
在这个例子中
be an image request and
是图像请求
[inaudible] hold on to the image
它将处理图像
and it's going to do all the
并为我们完成
work for us.
所有的工作
And as a result, we get back
结果是我们获得了
what we call observations, what
被称为观察结果的信息
did we observe in this image.
指的是在这个图像中我们观察到了什么
And these observations depend on
观察结果取决于
what you asked us to do.
请求的内容
So, we have classification
于是我们有了分类的观察结果
observation or detected objects.
或被检测的对象
Now when you want to track
现在当你想在
something in the sequence like
该队列中追踪某个对象
the wakeboarder it's basically
如冲浪选手
the same concept.
基本概念是不变的
We have some asks, we have the
我们有了询问
machinery, and we get some
处理设备
results out of it in the end.
最终可以获得结果
Again, the asks are requests.
重申一次  询问就是请求
Now since this changes with
因为对每一帧
every frame the image actually
的请求都在变化
travels with the request.
图像实际上在随着请求移动
Our machinery is again
我们的设备
[inaudible] request handler it's
也就是请求处理器
the sequence request handler and
会通过队列请求处理器处理请求
we get results which are
于是我们获得被称作观察结果的结果
observations that go with our
它们符合
requests.
我们的请求
So, let me talk a little bit
让我来进一步介绍
more about these two image
刚刚提到的
request handlers that I
两个
mentioned so far.
图像请求处理器
So, we have the image request
我们的图像 Request Handler
handler that is mostly if you
可以处理
want to do something interactive
大部分你想要与图像
with the image.
交互的请求
You want to do multiple Vision
你想要在一个图像上
tasks on an image, sometimes you
完成多个 Vision 任务
actually do one and then based
有时其实你只做了一个
on the results you then kick off
然后根据结果开始
the next one and that's what you
下一个任务
want to use the image request
这就是你想要使用图像 Request Handler
handler for.
完成的
It'll hold on to the image that
它将在整个处理过程中
it's set up with for its
保留图像
lifecycle and that allows us
因此我们可以
under the cover to do
在其中进行
performance optimizations by
性能优化
holding on to intermediates to
通过保留中间产物
make these requests perform
让请求的处理速度
faster.
加快
On the flipside, if I want to
另一方面
track something we use the
如果想要追踪某一对象
sequence request handler.
我们会使用 Sequence Request Handler（队列请求处理器）
The sequence request handler
Sequence Request Handler
allows us to keep tracking
让我们能够
[inaudible] in the sequence
在处理器中
request handler.
追踪对象
And it will not hold on to all
它不会
the images that gets fed into it
在处理过程中
over its lifecycle so they get
保留所有的图像
released earlier.
因此图像会被提前释放
But that means on the flipside,
但另一方面  这也意味着
you cannot do the same
如果你想在同一个图像上完成
optimizations if you want to do
多个请求
multiple requests on the same
你将无法
image.
进行优化
So how does this look in the
所以该功能的代码实现是怎样的呢
code, we are developers that's
作为开发人员
what we want to see.
这是我们想知道的
So, we start as a blank slate
首先从空白开始
that's always good and then we
这是我们乐于见到的
create a request.
然后创建一个请求
In this case, it's a face
在这里
detection request.
是一个人脸识别请求
Now we create the request
现在我们来创建 Request Handler
handler, what I'm choosing here
现在我选择的是
is a request handler based on
基于文件的 Request Handler
the files so I have a file on
因为磁盘上
disk that I want to use.
有我想要使用的文件
Now I ask myRequestHandler to
现在我询问 myRequestHandler
perform my request and this in
来完成我的请求
this case [inaudible] it's just
在这里
one request I have my array, but
我的数组中只有一个请求
it could be many and I get my
而实际上可以有很多
observations back.
我得到了我的观察结果
And this can be many faces that
我可以检测到
I detected.
很多个面部
Now the one thing I would like
在此我要强调的一点是
to highlight here is the results
结果会作为
come back as part of the request
请求的一部分被返回
that we actually set up
该请求就是我们
initially.
最初创建的
How does it look when we want to
当我们想追踪某物体时
track something?
代码又是什么样的呢
We create a sequence request
我们创建一个
handler [inaudible] of course
Sequence Request Handler
not set up as an image because
当然不设置为图像
we have to [inaudible] all the
因为我们需要处理
frames of the sequence.
队列中的每一帧
So, I started with an
因此我可以从
observation that I got from the
先前检测的
previous detection or I mark
观察结果开始
something up and I create my
或者我可以自行设置
tracking request.
创建自己的追踪请求
And I simply have to run the
我只需要运行
request.
这个请求
And I feed in in this case as a
在这里我输入的是
pixel buffer the frame that is
PixelBuffer
currently being dragged.
就是正在拖动的帧
And out of it again I get some
然后从处理器中
results.
我得到了结果
So, now that we have talked
我们已经说明了
about how this API is kind of
这个 API 是如何结构化的
structured I would like to guide
我想向你们展示
you through some best practices
一些优秀的实践事例
so that you get, you know, the
让你们知道 Vision
best experience out of Vision.
最佳的体验是怎样的
So, when we want to put together
当我们需要完成
a Computer Vision task you have
一件计算机视觉任务时
to think about a few things.
你需要考虑几件事情
Number one, what is the right
第一
image type that I want to use.
我想使用哪种图像类型
Number two, what am I going to
第二
do with the image.
我要对图像进行哪些处理
And number three, what
第三
performance do I need or want.
我需要或想要什么性能
Of course, you always want
当然你会想要
fastest, but there are some
最快的
tradeoffs that you have to think
但你必须在许多因素之间
about.
做出折衷
So, let's talk about the image
那么让我们讨论一下
type.
图像类型
Vision supports a number of
Vision 支持很多
CVPixelBuffer, CGIImage or even
从 CVPixelBuffer 到 CGIImage
as we saw in the previous
甚至还有之前例子中的
example just from data that I
NSData
use in NSURL.
和 NSURL
And we go over all these types
在下面的几页中
in the following slides so that
我们会一一展示这些图像类型
you know what to choose when.
让你知道何时选择何种类型
Which to choose depends a lot of
这很多因素决定的
like what you want to do.
比如你想要做什么
If you run from a camera stream
从相机流
or if you run from files on disk
或磁盘文件运行是不一样的
you have to look at that
你需要确定这一点
[inaudible] kind of which type
因为它决定了
of image you want to use.
你想要选择何种图像
Now two important things to
要记住重要的两点
remember is we already have an
我们已经在 Vision 框架中
imaging pipeline in the Vision
加入图像流水线
framework you don't need to
你不需要
scale the images.
对图像进行缩放
So, unless you already have a
因此除非
very small representation that
你已经有绝对要使用的
you absolutely want to use,
小图像
please don't pre-scale because
请不要预先压缩图像
we'll just do the work twice.
因为这样的话我们就会重复工作
And mind the orientation.
此外  还要注意图像方向
Computer Vision algorithms are
计算机视觉算法大多数时候
mostly not, you know, sensitive
(对方向不敏感)
to orientation or sorry, they
对不起
are sensitive to orientation so
它们对方向敏感
you have to pass that in.
所以你需要确认传入的图像
And that is an important part
这是非常重要的
because if you pass in a
因为如果你传入了
portrait image that's actually
横向侧放的
lying on its side we will not
肖像图像
find the faces and that's one of
我们将无法找到面部
the common mistakes that usually
这也是经常发生的
happens.
常见错误
So, I promised to go over the
让我们来看看
types.
各种图像类型
When you want to do something
当你想要完成与流相关的处理时
streaming we want to use the
可以使用
CVPixelBuffer.
CVPixelBuffer
When you create a VideoDataOut
当你创建 VideoDataOut 时
[inaudible] capture you will get
你会得到
CMSampleBuffers and through
CMSampleBuffers
those we get your
我们将从中获得你的
CVPixelBuffers.
CVPixelBuffers
It's also a pretty good format
这也是一个很好的图像格式
if you already have something
如果你已经
where you keep your image data
将你的原始图像数据如 LGB Pixel
raw in memory like it's LGB
保存在存储器中
pixels and wrap them into a
将它们打包成为
CVPixelBuffer this is a great
CVPixelBuffer
format to pass into Vision.
这是传入 Vision 很好的格式
When you get files from disk
如果你从磁盘上获得文件
please use the URL or if it
请使用 URL
comes from the web use the
如果它来源于网络
NSData path.
请使用 NSData 路径
The great thing about that is it
最棒的是
really allows us to reduce the
它让我们能够减少
memory for print in your
为你在应用中打印所分配的
application.
内存
Vision will only read what it
Vision 将只会读取
needs to perform the task.
完成任务需要的数据
If you think about you want to
如果你想要在
do face detection on a
6400 万像素的全景中
64-megapixel panorama Vision
做人脸识别
will actually reduce your memory
Vision 会真正降低所需内存
for it, but not reading the full
它不会将完整文件
file actually into the memory
读入内存
and that is an important thing
这一点
to keep in mind.
要牢记
We will read in this case the
这个例子中我们会从文件
EXIF Orientation out of the
读取 EXIF Orientation
file, but you can override it if
你也可以重写
you have to for those formats
如果图像格式
that don't support it.
不支持该操作的话
If you're already using Core
如果你已经在应用中
Image in your application by all
使用 Core Image
means process the CI image.
那当然应该传入 CI image
This is also important when you
当你想做一些
want to actually do some
预处理时
preprocessing.
这也非常重要
If you have some domain
如果你有专业知识
knowledge of what you want to do
知道你想在计算机视觉任务
in your Computer Vision task you
中做什么
can do some preprocessing and
你可以做一些预处理
try and enhance the image and,
尝试加强图像
therefore, enhance the Vision
这样可以加强
results.
Vision 的结果
If you want to learn a bit more
如果你想了解更多关于
about Core Image, there's a
Core Image 的信息
session on Thursday at 1:50 and
周四 1:50 有相关会议
they will also show the
他们将展示 Core Image
integration with our Vision
与 Vision 框架
framework.
的集成
Last but not least, if you have
最后但同样重要的是
all the images in your UI you
对于你应用界面中的所有图像
can use the CG image [inaudible]
你可以使用 CGimage
out of the NS image or the UI
转化 NSimage 或 UIimage
images let's say it comes from
它来自
the UI image picker and pass
UIImagePicker
those into Vision.
并将它们传入 Vision
Now what am I going to do with
如果我想对图像进行操作
the image and that's where we
现在就要决定
have to decide if I want to do
我是否想与图像进行交互
something interactive with the
如果想要与其交互
image in that case I use my
就要使用
ImageRequestHandler.
Image Request Handler（图像请求处理器）
It will hold on to the image for
它会保留图像
the time and I can do multiple
让我可以在图像上
passes on that image and get the
做多种操作
best results out of that.
获得最好的结果
Now the CVPixelBuffer
现在 CVPixelBuffer
technically will allow you that
在技术上可以允许你
you could change the pixels
更改输入图像的像素
[inaudible], but we see them as
但我们将图像视作不可变的
immutable so don't do that
因此不要尝试更改
because we'll get some strange
因为如果那样我们会得到
results.
奇怪的结果
Next, if you want to track
那么如果你想追踪
something we use the
某个对象
SequenceRequestHandler.
我们会使用 Sequence Request Handler
It allows us to keep the
它让我们始终保持
tracking state and lifecycle of
追踪的状态
my image is not tied to those
并且图像与 Request Handler
requests handler anymore, but
不再紧密相关
just how long it needs it for
只保留需要追踪的
the tracking.
时间
Performance, so these Vision
性能上
tasks are computationally
这些 Vision 任务经常需要密集计算
intensive very often and they do
很花时间
take time, so you have to think
因此你需要考虑
about that you want to actually
事实上不在主队列中
run your task on a different
而是换一个其他队列
queue not your main queue.
运行任务
And think about if you want to
你还要考虑是否要
do it in the background, which
在后台完成
is a bit slower or if you need
这可能会有点慢
it very quickly use a more
若要得到更快的性能
interactive quality of service
你需要使用
to get the performance.
交互质量更高的服务
A good practice is to use the
一个很好的例子是使用
completion handler to get the
Completion Handler
results back, this is part of
获得结果
our API.
它也是我们 API 的一部分
But keep in mind that this
但要记住
completion handler gets called
Completion Handler 只会获得
on that queue in which you
触发它的队列
actually set it off.
的结果
So, if you need to update your
因此如果你需要
UI you have to dispatch that
更新 UI
back to the main queue.
你需要把它派回主队列中
So as Brett already highlighted,
正如 Brett 已经强调的那样
we have a new face detection and
我们有新的人脸识别技术
you might say oh God, yet
你可能会说
another one.
天哪又来一个
But we have good reasons for
但我们有充足的理由
this.
这么做
Vision uses deep learning and
Vision 使用深度学习
this gives us really a lot
这让我们获得了
better precision and recall,
更高的准确度和更多的重调用
therefore, much better results.
因此会有更好的结果
The downside of it, on older
它的缺点在于
hardware it will run a bit
在较旧的硬件上
slower.
运行速度较慢
So, let's look a little bit at
让我们看一下
our overall landscape of face
我们提供的
detectors that we have
人脸识别的
available.
整体格局
So, we have Vision which really
我们有 Vision
gives us the best results and
它能给我们最好的结果
it's pretty fast and also pretty
运行速度很快
good in its power use as it is
能耗也很优秀
optimized for that.
因为它专门对此做了优化
And we have it available on all
我们在除 watchOS 之外
platforms except the watchOS.
所有平台上提供它
And this is the same in terms of
Core Image
availability for Core Image and
提供情况也相同
it's a bit faster, but the
它更快
results are not quite as good.
但结果没有 Vision 那么好
In the AV capture session which
在 AV Capture Session 中
is only happening during the
我们只在
capture side we can actually use
捕捉的部分
hardware so it's really fast in
使用了硬件
performance, but the results
所以运行的很快
again are not as good as we get
但结果还是
out of Vision.
不如 Vision 的
So, you have to choose depending
因此你需要根据
on your application what you
你的应用
want to do choose the right
以及你想要做什么
technology for the face
为人脸识别选择
detection.
合适的技术
Now I did mention that our
我有提到我们的质量
quality is better, so let me try
更好
to prove that a little bit.
现在让我稍加证明
So, I have here an image and I
我这里有一个图像
ran the face detection through
这是通过 Core Image
Core Image.
运行人脸识别
And we find two faces and we see
我们找到了两张脸
roughly where the eyes and where
模糊的看出了眼睛和嘴巴的
the mouth are.
位置
Now in Vision we find all four
在 Vision 中
faces even the occluded ones and
我们找到了全部四张脸  包括被遮挡的
we get a whole lot more details
通过人脸特征点我们还找到了
with the visual landmarks.
更加丰富的细节
Speaking of Core Image, I would
说到 Core Image
like to highlight a little bit
我想要强调的一点是
what's happening with the
CIDetectors
CIDetectors.
将会怎样
So, whoever uses it already can
现在已经使用它的人
keep on using them they are
还可以继续使用
still in Core Image, but all new
它仍在 Core Image 中
parts and all the improvements
但随着电脑发展
in terms of algorithms for
所有算法上
computer moving forward will be
出现的新的部分和改进
in Vision that's the new home
都将在 Vision 中体现
for Computer Vision.
Vision 是计算机视觉的新家
So, an awful lot of sides, how
好了说了这么久
about a demo.
让我们看一个 Demo
So, what I'm going to show you
我将向你们展示的
is an application that runs an
是一个运行着
AV capture session on the device
AV Capture Session 设备上的应用
if the demo Gods are with us.
希望演示顺利
And we will do a very simple
我们将会做非常简单的
rectangle detection request.
矩形检测请求
So, what do I have to do to set
那么我为什么要设置
this up?
这些呢
What you see here is I create my
你们看到的是
request, that's my simple
我创建了请求
rectangle detection request in
在本例中也就是
this case.
简单的矩形检测请求
I'm actually in the wrong sample
我开错了窗口
that's why I'm getting confused
刚刚才有点迷茫
here, my apologies.
不好意思
Here we go.
好了开始
Okay we have our rectangle
我们已经有了矩形检测请求
detection request and I'm
我会设定
setting some parameters just as
一些参数
an example here, I only want
作为例子
them this minimum size in our
我想要在坐标系中
coordinates are normalized so I
标准化最小尺寸
only want a 10% minimize size of
我只想要 10%
the image and I just want 20
最小化图片的大小
rectangles.
并且我只想要 20 个矩形
I could get more, but I want 20,
我可以获得更多 但我只要 20
I just picked a number.
我只是挑了个数字
I set up my area of the request
我设定希望执行
that I want to perform and the
该请求的区域
right here this is our
这里是我们的
completion handler and all that
Completion Handler
I'm going to do is I'm going to
我要做的就是
draw my rectangles, but as you
画出矩形
notice I'm just patching it to
但你注意到我为了更新 UI
the main queue to update our UI.
把它移到主队列中
Where do our images come from?
我们的图像来自哪里？
So, we look at the capture
看到这里的
output here and as I promised,
捕获输出
in the capture output we get our
正向我说到的
pixelBuffer from the
我们从 CMSampleBuffer 中获得
CMSampleBuffer.
pixelBuffer
Right here I'm getting the
在这里我获得
cameraIntrinsics.
cameraIntrinsics 数据
Now this is something that is
这个在一些
important in some of these
计算机视觉的路径中
Computer Vision paths where we
非常重要
actually know what the camera is
能让我们知道摄像头
kind of looking at.
对着的方向
As I mentioned, we don't forget
就像我提到的那样
the acts of orientation and I
我们没有忘记 EXIF Orientation
create an image request handler
我创建了一个 Image Request Handler
and perform our tasks.
用以完成我们的任务
So, how does this look when we
当我们真正运行的时候
actually run it?
会发生什么？
All right, so what we're going
好的  现在我们
to see here is that now we
看到的是
tracked this rectangle and
我们在追踪这个矩形
that's as simple as it is, we
这很简单
can find other rectangles.
我们还可以找其他的矩形
If the cable is long enough we
如果连接线足够长
can actually look oh, there we
我们可以看到
find a computer with various
这里是一台电脑
rectangles.
有着许多矩形
Now I chose the yellow kind of
我是特意选择黄色标识的
on purpose because it's the same
因为它与
color as you saw in the demo
你在新投影机
during the keynote for the new
主旨演讲的 Demo
document camera on notes.
中看到的是同一颜色
And I borrowed their color
我借用了他们的颜色
because they borrowed our code
因为他们借用了我们的代码
to do actually the rectangle
来做这些
detection.
矩形检测
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
Thank you.
谢谢
Now that was simple, let's do a
到现在为止很简单
bit more.
让我们加点难度
So, how about we throw some
把机器学习
machine learning at this as well
加进来怎么样
just for the fun of it.
为了更有意思
So, what I have to do is I have
因此我要做的就是
a little model that I just
我把这个小模型
dragged into my project here.
拖进了我的工程文件中
And that is a classifier that
这是一个分类器
will tell us a bit something
可以告诉我们关于图像的
about the image.
一些信息
And we see when we look at this
在这一部分我们看到
part here that we need to feed
我们需要输入
it an image of a very strange
许多不同尺寸的图像
size and get out of it some
然后得到
classification.
分类
Now you don't need to worry
现在你不需要担心尺寸
about that size because Vision
因为 Vision
will do the work for you.
会帮你处理
So, what do I need to do?
我需要做什么
I first need to create a Vision
首先我需要创建一个 Vision 模型
model and my request with that.
并添加我的请求
And that is the part that we
也就是这一部分的功能
have here, so I'm simply loading
我简单的加载了
the inception model and I create
初始模型
my classification request.
并创建了我的分类请求
Now it tells me there's
它提示我
something missing and I will get
缺少参数
to that in just a moment.
我一会儿会来处理
The last thing I want to
最后一件我想要
highlight here is it says that
在这里强调的事是
it was okay square image, but
会存在正方形的图像
our cameras don't see squares so
但我们的摄像头不会分辨正方形
I need to tell it actually how
我需要告诉它怎样去处理正方形
to handle just, you know, the
你知道的
aspect ratio that I want to use.
我要使用什么样的长宽比
And I say okay I want to just
因此我需要
send a crop.
进行设置
So, I need a completion handler
我的任务
for my task and I have that
需要一个 Completion Handler
already pre canned here as well.
我也提前设置好了
So, in this completion handler I
在  Completion Handler 中
simply look at my observation
我只是看到了观察结果
and I will get so this
这个分类器
classifier can see a thousand
有许多不同的信息
different things and I don't
我不需要全部展示
want to show all of them I only
我只展示
show the ones that I care about.
我重视的部分
So, what I'm doing is a little
我在这里做的是
bit of filtering, I only take
一些简单的筛选
the top four and I only look at
我只看前 4 个
the ones that have a confidence
并且准确度
of at least 30%, it just works
至少达到 30%
well for my demo here, but you
这个条件非常适合我的 Demo
know you will figure out what
你需要找到适合
kind of works well for your
自己模型
model.
的条件
And all I have to do next is add
我下一步要做的是
my classification request into
把我的分类请求添加至
my area of request and now I
我的请求范围中
will actually run two requests.
我实际上运行了两个请求
So, I have this already loaded
我已经将它加载到
on my device, let's see how this
我的设备上
actually looks.
让我们看看会是什么结果
Of course, you will see it when
当然只有我切换到正确的设备
I switch to the correct machine,
你们才能看到
there we go.
开始
Okay, so we have a coffee mug
所以我们看到了一个空的
which is empty, somebody better
咖啡杯
fill that for me.
最好有人能帮我倒满它
We have a ballpoint pen, we have
这是一个圆珠笔
a padlock and look an iPod.
这是一个挂锁  看  这是一个 iPod
Who has stolen those empty cards
偷走这些空卡的人
away and didn't realize it was
肯定没意识到
an iPod?
它是 iPod
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
All right, let's go back to the
好的  让我们回到幻灯片
slides before we get to the next
之后再进行下一次的
show-and-tell.
展示说明。
For my next demo, I want to do
我的下一个 Demo 中
something a little bit more
我想要做一些
elaborate and with that I chose
更复杂的事情
something that's called
因此我选择了
MNISTVision.
MNISTVision
People in the machine learning
机器语言学习社区中的人
community have already looked at
对这个
that a little bit more.
比较熟悉
MNIST is a dataset where a bunch
MNIST 是一个数据集
of government employees and high
许多政府雇员和高校学生
school students wrote numbers
在其中写下数据
down and this was marked up and
它们被标记
people were trained in our
进行标记的分类器
classifier on that.
是人们训练的
Note this is basically like
请注意这些基本是
white numbers on black
白色的数字
background, so I guess they've
写在黑色的背景上
written it with chalk on an old
我猜想是用白粉笔
blackboard.
写在旧黑板上的
So, in this sample code I'm
我要用这段简单的代码
going to show you I want to show
向你们展示
a few concepts that are kind of
一些概念
important like making something
它们非常重要
a bit more elaborate with
比如如何用 Vision
Vision.
完成复杂的任务
First, we'll spin off model
首先我们
requests based on top of each
一层一层的叠加请求
other then we use Core Image in
这个过程中我们使用 Core Image
between to do some image process
进行图像处理
and last but not least, we use
最后也是最重要的是
Core ML again for the machine
再次使用 Core ML
learning part.
进行机器学习
So, how is this going to work?
结果会是怎样的呢？
We have here an image on which
这里有一张图像
we find a sticky note.
上面贴着便利贴
Well we find it by using the
我们可以通过
rectangle detector, there's our
矩形检测
sticky note.
找到便利贴
Now that is prospectively
现在有一点点不一样
distorted and it's clearly not
它明显不是
white text on black background.
黑底白字
So, we use Core Image in the
下一步我们使用
next step and we'll actually do
Core Image
the perspective correction of it
进行视角调整
and invert the color and enhance
并转换颜色
also the contrast so that we get
增强对比度
rid this black-and-white image.
因此我们得到了这张黑白的图像
And last but not least, I need
最后也是最重要的
to run my MNIST classifier on it
我需要运行我的 MNIST 分类器
and it should tell me that this
它应该告诉我
is the number four and this has
这是数字 4
80% confidence that this is the
这是数字 4 的
number four.
准确性在 80% 以上
Again, let's see how this looks
我们再来看看它在
in the app.
App 中是怎么显示的
So again, I start off as a
我再次打开
rectangle detector request, it's
矩形检测请求
my favorite I know.
这是我最喜欢的部分
But it's more interesting what
但我即将在
I'm going to do in the
Completion Handler 中做的
completion handler.
更加有趣
So, I do some validation just to
我进行了验证
make sure that the rectangles
确保得到的
I'm getting out of it are
矩形
actually okay.
是正确的
But the interesting part happens
但这里是
here.
最有趣的部分
I get the coordinates of the
我得到了四个顶点的坐标
corners and feed them into CI to
把它们传入 CI
use the CIPerspectiveCorrection.
使用 CIPerspectiveCorrection
That allows me to take this
这使得我能够处理
prospectively distorted image
视角扭曲的图像
and actually bring it upright as
将它恢复成
if I would have the camera
直立拍摄的
straight on.
图像
I use the CIColorControls to
我使用 CIColorControls
really bring out the contrast of
提高图像的对比度
the image to make it kind of
将它
binarized.
二进制化
And as I said, I have to color
像我说过的
invert it.
我要改变图像的颜色
Now the resulting image of that
现在得到了结果图像
I feed into a new request in
我输入一个新的请求
there because we have a new
因为我将在
image on which I'll run the
新的图像上
classification.
运行分类
So, how does the classification
分类看上去
look like?
是什么样的
The classification for that I
这个分类我已经
use my endless model which I
用我的大型模型
actually have ready and this is
做好了
a small model that I've really
这是一个小型模型
trained actually on this laptop
我已经在这台笔记本电脑上训练完成了
very easily give us a few lines
非常简单
of code script and then thanks
只有几行代码
to Core ML I can just drag that
感谢 Core ML 我可以
in and use this very easily.
把它拖拽进来并轻松地使用
So, I have my model here.
这是我的模型
Now again, this one part I would
我再次强调这点
like to highlight this, so that
本例中使用的是
takes in this case a very small
是一个非常小的
grayscale image.
灰度图像
So, an image 28 by 28 pixels it
它应该可以在
should be able to read these
28 x 28 像素的图像中
numbers.
读取那些数字
So that's where my
这就是我的
classification is coming from
分类器
and now I need to feed in the
现在我需要输入
image.
图像
So, this sample code has been
这段代码
made available also for the
在会话中
session to make it easy also to
可用
run a simulator not running it
这样就能够轻松的运行模拟器
live off of the camera I'm just
而不需要使用摄像头实时的画面
going to use actually the
实际上我要用
UIImagePicker and feed it into
UIImagePicker 将它输入到
my VMImageRequestHandler and let
我的 VMImageRequestHandler 中
it just perform the rectangle
让它运行
request.
矩形检测
Now notice I buried the request
请注意我把分类的请求
for the classification into the
放在了我的
completion handler of my
矩形检测
rectangle detection and that
里
allows us to basically cascade
这让我们能够
multiple requests on top of each
叠加
other.
多个请求
So, let's try the demo for this.
让我们试试这个 Demo
Okay, so I have my app here and
我的 App 在这里
well [inaudible] giveaway.
不要被看到了
Okay, so what I see here is
好的  这里我们看到的
again I have my image on the
是上方的图像
top, this was actually the photo
它是我稍早时候
that I took earlier.
拍摄的照片
We see its correctly classifying
我们看到它被正确的分类为
as a number one, it was a really
数字 1
high confidence in this case.
这个例子中准确度很高
And what you see on the bottom
下方的图片
is just basically just to
仅仅是视觉化了
visualize that I took this
中间图像
intermediate image that we
它是在
created in CI and show this as
CI 中被创建的
well.
显示的也是同样的数字
Let's choose another number.
让我们选另一个数字
Yes, this is the number three.
是的这是数字 3
Can we guess what this number
猜这个数字是多少
is, it's the number four?
这是数字 4
It works correctly.
运行结果正确
All right, thank you.
好的谢谢大家
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
Let me go back to our slides.
让我们回到幻灯片
So that is our Vision framework.
这就是我们的 Vision 框架
Let's capitalize a little bit on
让我们总结一下
what we really have seen here.
之前看到的内容
So, Vision is a high-level
Vision 是计算机视觉的
framework for Computer Vision
高级框架
and it should really make it
它让你在应用中
easy for you to use this in your
能够轻松的使用
applications even if you're not
就算你不是
a Computer Vision expert.
计算机视觉专家
We have various detectors and
我们有很多探测器
there's a whole variety of that
各种各样
and they all run through one
他们都运行于
consistent interface which would
统一的界面上
make it very easy to learn that
使得了解这组 API
set of APIs.
变得非常容易
And last but not least, the
最后也是最重要的
integration with Core ML.
是与 Core ML 的集成
By bringing your own custom
通过使用你的自定义模型
models you can do a lot in your
你可以在应用中完成很多事情
application, you can find
你可以找到热狗
hotdogs and see if they are
并且判断
really hotdogs.
它们是不是真的热狗
I had to make that joke.
开个玩笑
So, if you want to learn more
如果你想了解关于本节会议的更多信息
about our session, please go to
请前往
our website and I would
我们的网站
definitely highlight there are
我一定要强调
some related sessions that you
一些相关会议
should have watched perhaps in
你们可能之前
the past.
已经听过
I'll read you the Core ML one,
我列出了关于 Core ML 的
but you can find it on our
你也可以在我们的网站上
website.
找到它
Please come for our get-together
欢迎参加
that we have at 6:30 today, chat
今天 6:30 的聚会
about what we can do.
讨论我们的工作
And for the little bit more
关于 Core ML
advanced part of Core ML there's
更高级的内容
a session on Thursday, as well
周四会有一节会议
as we have a session with Core
我们也会有一节 Core Image 的会议
Image where they will also do
他们会在会上
some very fancy stuff with Core
展示 Core Image 和 Vision
Image and Vision.
的神奇功能
And with that I'd like to thank
感谢你们今天的到来
you for coming today and enjoy
希望你们享受
the rest of WWDC.
接下来 WWDC 的内容
Thank you.
谢谢大家
[ Applause ]
[掌声]